/* global define */
define(function(require, exports, module) {
	
	module.exports = {
		displayName: 'JLPT N5 Vocabulary',
		items: [{ front: 'Ah!', back: 'ああ' },
				{ front: 'to meet', back: 'あう' },
				{ front: 'blue', back: 'あおい' },
				{ front: 'red', back: 'あかい' },
				{ front: 'light, bright', back: 'あかるい' },
				{ front: 'autumn, fall', back: 'あき' },
				{ front: 'open', back: 'あく' },
				{ front: 'to open', back: 'あける' },
				{ front: 'to give', back: 'あげる' },
				{ front: 'morning', back: 'あさ' },
				{ front: 'breakfast', back: 'あさごはん' },
				{ front: 'the day after tomorrow', back: 'あさって' },
				{ front: 'leg, foot', back: 'あし' },
				{ front: 'tomorrow', back: 'あした' },
				{ front: 'over there', back: 'あそこ' },
				{ front: 'to play', back: 'あそぶ' },
				{ front: 'warm', back: 'あたたかい' },
				{ front: 'head', back: 'あたま' },
				{ front: 'new', back: 'あたらしい' },
				{ front: 'over there (polite)', back: 'あちら' },
				{ front: 'hot (air)', back: 'あつい' },
				{ front: 'thick', back: 'あつい' },
				{ front: 'later, after', back: 'あと' },
				{ front: 'you', back: 'あなた' },
				{ front: 'older brother', back: 'あに' },
				{ front: 'older sister', back: 'あね' },
				{ front: 'that (over there)', back: 'あの' },
				{ front: 'well, then', back: 'あの' },
				{ front: 'apartment', back: 'アパート' },
				{ front: 'to take a shower', back: 'あびる' },
				{ front: 'dangerous', back: 'あぶない' },
				{ front: 'sweet', back: 'あまい' },
				{ front: 'not so', back: 'あまり' },
				{ front: 'rain', back: 'あめ' },
				{ front: 'to wash', back: 'あらう' },
				{ front: 'to be, to exist', back: 'ある' },
				{ front: 'to possess', back: 'ある' },
				{ front: 'to walk', back: 'あるく' },
				{ front: 'that one', back: 'あれ' },
				{ front: 'good', back: 'いい / よい' },
				{ front: 'no', back: 'いいえ' },
				{ front: 'to say, to tell', back: 'いう' },
				{ front: 'house, home', back: 'いえ' },
				{ front: 'to go', back: 'いく' },
				{ front: 'how many, how old', back: 'いくつ' },
				{ front: 'how much', back: 'いくら' },
				{ front: 'pond', back: 'いけ' },
				{ front: 'doctor', back: 'いしゃ' },
				{ front: 'chair', back: 'いす' },
				{ front: 'to be busy', back: 'いそがしい' },
				{ front: 'to be painful', back: 'いたい' },
				{ front: 'one', back: 'いち' },
				{ front: 'one day', back: 'いちにち' },
				{ front: 'No. 1, the best, the first', back: 'いちばん' },
				{ front: 'when', back: 'いつ' },
				{ front: 'the 5th day of the month, 5 days', back: 'いつか' },
				{ front: 'together', back: 'いっしょ' },
				{ front: 'five', back: 'いつつ' },
				{ front: 'always', back: 'いつも' },
				{ front: 'now', back: 'いま' },
				{ front: 'meaning', back: 'いみ' },
				{ front: 'someone’s younger sister', back: 'いもうと' },
				{ front: 'not likable, unpleasant', back: 'いや' },
				{ front: 'entrance', back: 'いりぐち' },
				{ front: 'need, must have, be required', back: 'いる' },
				{ front: 'to exist', back: 'いる' },
				{ front: 'to insert, to put in', back: 'いれる' },
				{ front: 'color', back: 'いろ' },
				{ front: 'various', back: 'いろいろ' },
				{ front: 'top, on, above', back: 'うえ' },
				{ front: 'back, rear, behind', back: 'うしろ' },
				{ front: 'thin', back: 'うすい' },
				{ front: 'song', back: 'うた' },
				{ front: 'to sing', back: 'うたう' },
				{ front: 'home', back: 'うち' },
				{ front: 'to be born', back: 'うまれる' },
				{ front: 'sea', back: 'うみ' },
				{ front: 'to sell', back: 'うる' },
				{ front: 'coat, jacket', back: 'うわぎ' },
				{ front: 'picture', back: 'え' },
				{ front: 'movie', back: 'えいが' },
				{ front: 'cinema', back: 'えいがかん' },
				{ front: 'English language', back: 'えいご' },
				{ front: 'Yes, I see', back: 'ええ' },
				{ front: 'station', back: 'えき' },
				{ front: 'elevator', back: 'エレベータ' },
				{ front: 'Yen', back: 'えん' },
				{ front: 'pencil', back: 'えんぴつ' },
				{ front: 'honorific prefix', back: 'お' },
				{ front: 'tasty, delicious', back: 'おいしい' },
				{ front: 'big', back: 'おおきい' },
				{ front: 'many people', back: 'おおぜい' },
				{ front: 'my own mother', back: 'おかあさん' },
				{ front: 'confectionary, cake', back: 'おかし' },
				{ front: 'money', back: 'おかね' },
				{ front: 'to get up, to stand up', back: 'おきる' },
				{ front: 'to put, to place', back: 'おく' },
				{ front: 'someone’s wife', back: 'おくさん' },
				{ front: 'to send', back: 'おくる' },
				{ front: 'alcohol, sake', back: 'おさけ' },
				{ front: 'plate', back: 'おさら' },
				{ front: 'uncle', back: 'おじさん' },
				{ front: 'grand father', back: 'おじいさん' },
				{ front: 'to push', back: 'おす' },
				{ front: 'late, slow', back: 'おそい' },
				{ front: 'tea', back: 'おちゃ' },
				{ front: 'toilet, lavatory', back: 'おてあらい' },
				{ front: 'father', back: 'おとうさん' },
				{ front: 'someone’s younger brother', back: 'おとうと' },
				{ front: 'man', back: 'おとこ' },
				{ front: 'boy', back: 'おとこのこ' },
				{ front: 'the day before yesterday', back: 'おととい' },
				{ front: 'the year before last', back: 'おととし' },
				{ front: 'adult', back: 'おとな' },
				{ front: 'stomach', back: 'おなか' },
				{ front: 'same', back: 'おなじ' },
				{ front: 'someone’s elder brother', back: 'おにいさん' },
				{ front: 'someone’s elder sister', back: 'おねえさん' },
				{ front: 'aunt', back: 'おばさん' },
				{ front: 'grandmother', back: 'おばあさん' },
				{ front: 'lunchbox', back: 'おべんとう' },
				{ front: 'to memorize, to remember', back: 'おぼえる' },
				{ front: 'heavy', back: 'おもい' },
				{ front: 'interesting, funny', back: 'おもしろい' },
				{ front: 'to swim', back: 'およぐ' },
				{ front: 'to get off', back: 'おりる' },
				{ front: 'to end', back: 'おわる' },
				{ front: 'music', back: 'おんがく' },
				{ front: 'woman', back: 'おんな' },
				{ front: 'girl', back: 'おんなのこ' },
				{ front: '~times', back: '〜かい' },
				{ front: '~floor', back: '〜かい' },
				{ front: 'foreign country', back: 'がいこく' },
				{ front: 'foreigner', back: 'がいこくじん' },
				{ front: 'company, enterprise', back: 'かいしゃ' },
				{ front: 'stairs', back: 'かいだん' },
				{ front: 'shopping', back: 'かいもの' },
				{ front: 'to buy', back: 'かう' },
				{ front: 'to return an object', back: 'かえす' },
				{ front: 'to return home', back: 'かえる' },
				{ front: 'face', back: 'かお' },
				{ front: 'to take time, money', back: 'かかる' },
				{ front: 'key', back: 'かぎ' },
				{ front: 'to write', back: 'かく' },
				{ front: 'student', back: 'がくせい' },
				{ front: '~ number of months', back: '〜かげつ' },
				{ front: 'to wear', back: 'かける' },
				{ front: 'to make a phone call', back: 'かける' },
				{ front: 'umbrella', back: 'かさ' },
				{ front: 'to lend', back: 'かす' },
				{ front: 'wind', back: 'かぜ' },
				{ front: 'a cold', back: 'かぜ' },
				{ front: 'family', back: 'かぞく' },
				{ front: 'person (polite)', back: 'かた' },
				{ front: 'Katakana', back: 'かたかな' },
				{ front: 'January', back: 'いちがつ' },
				{ front: 'February', back: 'にがつ' },
				{ front: 'March', back: 'さんがつ' },
				{ front: 'April', back: 'しがつ' },
				{ front: 'May', back: 'ごがつ' },
				{ front: 'June', back: 'ろくがつ' },
				{ front: 'July', back: 'しちがつ' },
				{ front: 'August', back: 'はちがつ' },
				{ front: 'September', back: 'くがつ' },
				{ front: 'October', back: 'じゅうがつ' },
				{ front: 'November', back: 'じゅういちがつ' },
				{ front: 'December', back: 'じゅうにがつ' },
				{ front: 'school', back: 'がっこう' },
				{ front: 'corner', back: 'かど' },
				{ front: 'my wife', back: 'かない' },
				{ front: 'bag', back: 'かばん' },
				{ front: 'vase', back: 'かびん' },
				{ front: 'to put on a hat', back: 'かぶる' },
				{ front: 'paper', back: 'かみ' },
				{ front: 'camera', back: 'かめら' },
				{ front: 'Tuesday', back: 'かようび' },
				{ front: 'hot, spicy', back: 'からい' },
				{ front: 'body', back: 'からだ' },
				{ front: 'to borrow', back: 'かりる' },
				{ front: '3rd person wants to', back: '〜がります' },
				{ front: 'light (not heavy)', back: 'かるい' },
				{ front: 'calendar', back: 'カレンダー' },
				{ front: 'river', back: 'かわ' },
				{ front: '~side', back: '~がわ' },
				{ front: 'cute, pretty', back: 'かわいい' },
				{ front: 'Kanji character', back: 'かんじ' },
				{ front: 'tree', back: 'き' },
				{ front: 'yellow', back: 'きいろい' },
				{ front: 'to go out, to vanish', back: 'きえる' },
				{ front: 'to hear, to listen, to ask', back: 'きく' },
				{ front: 'north', back: 'きた' },
				{ front: 'guitar', back: 'ギター' },
				{ front: 'dirty', back: 'きたない' },
				{ front: 'coffee shop', back: 'きっさてん' },
				{ front: 'stamp', back: 'きって' },
				{ front: 'ticket', back: 'きっぷ' },
				{ front: 'yesterday', back: 'きのう' },
				{ front: 'nine', back: 'きゅう' },
				{ front: 'beef', back: 'ぎゅうにく' },
				{ front: 'milk', back: 'ぎゅうにゅう' },
				{ front: 'today', back: 'きょう' },
				{ front: 'class room', back: 'きょうしつ' },
				{ front: 'siblings', back: 'きょうだい' },
				{ front: 'last year', back: 'きょねん' },
				{ front: 'unpleasant, not likable', back: 'きらい' },
				{ front: 'to cut', back: 'きる' },
				{ front: 'to wear, to put on', back: 'きる' },
				{ front: 'to come', back: 'くる' },
				{ front: 'beautiful, clean', back: 'きれい' },
				{ front: 'kg', back: 'キロ' },
				{ front: 'km', back: 'キロ' },
				{ front: 'bank', back: 'ぎんこう' },
				{ front: 'Friday', back: 'きんようび' },
				{ front: 'nine', back: 'く' },
				{ front: 'medicine', back: 'くすり' },
				{ front: 'give me…', back: 'ください' },
				{ front: 'fruit', back: 'くだもの' },
				{ front: 'mouth', back: 'くち' },
				{ front: 'shoe', back: 'くつ' },
				{ front: 'socks', back: 'くつした' },
				{ front: 'country', back: 'くに' },
				{ front: 'cloudy weather', back: 'くもり' },
				{ front: 'dark', back: 'くらい' },
				{ front: 'about', back: 'ぐらい' },
				{ front: 'class', back: 'クラス' },
				{ front: 'gram', back: 'グラム' },
				{ front: 'car', back: 'くるま' },
				{ front: 'black', back: 'くろい' },
				{ front: 'this morning', back: 'けさ' },
				{ front: 'to turn off, switch off', back: 'けす' },
				{ front: 'fine, all right', back: 'けっこう' },
				{ front: 'marriage', back: 'けっこん' },
				{ front: 'Monday', back: 'げつようび' },
				{ front: 'entrance of a house', back: 'げんかん' },
				{ front: 'vigor, health, vitality', back: 'げんき' },
				{ front: 'counter for small objects', back: '〜こ' },
				{ front: 'five', back: 'ご' },
				{ front: '~ language', back: '〜ご' },
				{ front: 'park, large garden', back: 'こうえん' },
				{ front: 'police box', back: 'こうばん' },
				{ front: 'voice', back: 'こえ' },
				{ front: 'coat', back: 'コート' },
				{ front: 'here', back: 'ここ' },
				{ front: 'afternoon', back: 'ごご' },
				{ front: '9th day of a month, 9 days', back: 'ここのか' },
				{ front: 'nine', back: 'ここのつ' },
				{ front: 'someone else’s husband', back: 'ごしゅじん' },
				{ front: 'morning, a.m.', back: 'ごぜん' },
				{ front: 'to answer', back: 'こたえる' },
				{ front: 'this side, this place', back: 'こちら' },
				{ front: 'cup, glass', back: 'コップ' },
				{ front: 'this year', back: 'ことし' },
				{ front: 'phrase, language', back: 'ことば' },
				{ front: 'child', back: 'こども' },
				{ front: 'this…', back: 'この' },
				{ front: 'meal, cooked rice', back: 'ごはん' },
				{ front: 'to be in trouble', back: 'こまる' },
				{ front: 'this', back: 'これ' },
				{ front: 'around…', back: 'ごろ' },
				{ front: 'this month', back: 'こんげつ' },
				{ front: 'this week', back: 'こんしゅう' },
				{ front: 'this sort of, this kind of', back: 'こんな' },
				{ front: 'this evening', back: 'こんばん' },
				{ front: 'well…', back: 'さあ' },
				{ front: 'years old', back: '〜さい' },
				{ front: 'fish', back: 'さかな' },
				{ front: 'earlier, former', back: 'さき' },
				{ front: 'to blossom', back: 'さく' },
				{ front: 'composition', back: 'さくぶん' },
				{ front: 'to open an umbrella', back: 'さす' },
				{ front: 'counter for books', back: '〜さつ' },
				{ front: 'magazine', back: 'ざっし' },
				{ front: 'sugar', back: 'さとう' },
				{ front: 'cold', back: 'さむい' },
				{ front: 'the year after next year', back: 'さらいねん' },
				{ front: 'three', back: 'さん' },
				{ front: 'Mr., Mrs.', back: '〜さん' },
				{ front: 'to take a walk', back: 'さんぽ' },
				{ front: 'four', back: 'し' },
				{ front: 'o’clock', back: '〜じ' },
				{ front: 'salt', back: 'しお' },
				{ front: 'however, but', back: 'しかし' },
				{ front: 'time', back: 'じかん' },
				{ front: '~hours (classificator)', back: '〜じかん' },
				{ front: 'work', back: 'しごと' },
				{ front: 'dictionary', back: 'じしょ' },
				{ front: 'quiet', back: 'しずか' },
				{ front: 'under, below', back: 'した' },
				{ front: 'question', back: 'しつもん' },
				{ front: 'bicycle', back: 'じてんしゃ' },
				{ front: 'car, vehicle', back: 'じどうしゃ' },
				{ front: 'to die, to pas away', back: 'しぬ' },
				{ front: 'dictionary', back: 'じびき' },
				{ front: 'oneself', back: 'じぶん' },
				{ front: 'to close', back: 'しまる' },
				{ front: 'to close', back: 'しめる' },
				{ front: 'to fasten a seatbelt', back: 'しめる' },
				{ front: 'well, then', back: 'じゃ' },
				{ front: 'photo', back: 'しゃしん' },
				{ front: 'shirt', back: 'シャツ' },
				{ front: 'ten', back: 'じゅう' },
				{ front: '… weeks', back: '〜しゅうかん' },
				{ front: 'lesson, class', back: 'じゅぎょう' },
				{ front: 'homework', back: 'しゅくだい' },
				{ front: 'to be good at something', back: 'じょうず' },
				{ front: 'to be strong, durable', back: 'じょうぶ' },
				{ front: 'soy sauce', back: 'しょうゆ' },
				{ front: 'dining room, canteen', back: 'しょくどう' },
				{ front: 'to know', back: 'しる' },
				{ front: 'white', back: 'しろい' },
				{ front: '~an, ~ese (nationality)', back: '〜じん' },
				{ front: 'newspaper', back: 'しんぶん' },
				{ front: 'Wednesday', back: 'すいようび' },
				{ front: 'to breathe, to smoke', back: 'すう' },
				{ front: 'skirt', back: 'スカート' },
				{ front: 'to like', back: 'すき' },
				{ front: 'past, over', back: '〜すぎ' },
				{ front: 'at once', back: 'すぐに' },
				{ front: 'a little', back: 'すこし' },
				{ front: 'cool', back: 'すずしい' },
				{ front: 'each', back: '〜ずつ' },
				{ front: 'stove, heater', back: 'ストーブ' },
				{ front: 'spoon', back: 'スプーン' },
				{ front: 'sports', back: 'スポーツ' },
				{ front: 'trousers', back: 'ズボン' },
				{ front: 'to live, to reside somewhere', back: 'すむ' },
				{ front: 'slipper', back: 'スリッパ' },
				{ front: 'to do', back: 'する' },
				{ front: 'to sit', back: 'すわる' },
				{ front: 'height', back: 'せい' },
				{ front: 'student', back: 'せいと' },
				{ front: 'sweater', back: 'セーター' },
				{ front: 'soap', back: 'せっけん' },
				{ front: 'jacket, suit', back: 'せびろ' },
				{ front: 'narrow', back: 'せまい' },
				{ front: 'zero', back: 'ゼロ' },
				{ front: '1,000, thousand', back: 'せん' },
				{ front: 'last month', back: 'せんげつ' },
				{ front: 'last week', back: 'せんしゅう' },
				{ front: 'teacher', back: 'せんせい' },
				{ front: 'washing, to wash', back: 'せんたく' },
				{ front: 'all', back: 'ぜんぶ' },
				{ front: 'so', back: 'そう' },
				{ front: 'to clean', back: 'そうじ' },
				{ front: 'and then', back: 'そうして' },
				{ front: 'there', back: 'そこ' },
				{ front: 'there (polite)', back: 'そちら' },
				{ front: 'outside', back: 'そと' },
				{ front: 'that…', back: 'その' },
				{ front: 'next to', back: 'そば' },
				{ front: 'sky', back: 'そら' },
				{ front: 'that', back: 'それ' },
				{ front: 'after that', back: 'それから' },
				{ front: 'then, well', back: 'それでは' },
				{ front: 'counter for machines', back: '〜だい' },
				{ front: 'university', back: 'だいがく' },
				{ front: 'embassy', back: 'たいしかん' },
				{ front: 'OK', back: 'だいじょうぶ' },
				{ front: 'to be very fond of', back: 'だいすき' },
				{ front: 'very important', back: 'たいせつ' },
				{ front: 'mostly, usually', back: 'たいてい' },
				{ front: 'kitchen', back: 'だいどころ' },
				{ front: 'very, serious', back: 'たいへん' },
				{ front: 'high, expensive', back: 'たかい' },
				{ front: 'many, much', back: 'たくさん' },
				{ front: 'taxi', back: 'タクシー' },
				{ front: 'to take out, hand in', back: 'だす' },
				{ front: 'more than one, and others', back: '〜たち' },
				{ front: 'to stand', back: 'たつ' },
				{ front: 'building', back: 'たてもの' },
				{ front: 'pleasant, enjoyable', back: 'たのしい' },
				{ front: 'to ask, to request', back: 'たのむ' },
				{ front: 'cigarette', back: 'たばこ' },
				{ front: 'perhaps, probably', back: 'たぶん' },
				{ front: 'food', back: 'たべもの' },
				{ front: 'to eat', back: 'たべる' },
				{ front: 'egg', back: 'たまご' },
				{ front: 'who?', back: 'だれ' },
				{ front: 'birthday', back: 'たんじょうび' },
				{ front: 'gradually', back: 'だんだん' },
				{ front: 'small', back: 'ちいさい' },
				{ front: 'near, close', back: 'ちかい' },
				{ front: 'different', back: 'ちがう' },
				{ front: 'subway', back: 'ちかてつ' },
				{ front: 'map', back: 'ちず' },
				{ front: 'my father', back: 'ちち' },
				{ front: 'brown', back: 'ちゃいろ' },
				{ front: 'rice bowl', back: 'ちゃわん' },
				{ front: 'in the middle of', back: '〜ちゅう' },
				{ front: 'just', back: 'ちょうど' },
				{ front: 'a little', back: 'ちょっと' },
				{ front: 'the 1st day of a month', back: 'ついたち' },
				{ front: 'to use', back: 'つかう' },
				{ front: 'to get tired', back: 'つかれる' },
				{ front: 'next', back: 'つぎ' },
				{ front: 'to arrive', back: 'つく' },
				{ front: 'table', back: 'つくえ' },
				{ front: 'to make, to produce', back: 'つくる' },
				{ front: 'to turn on', back: 'つける' },
				{ front: 'to work for someone', back: 'つとめる' },
				{ front: 'uninteresting', back: 'つまらない' },
				{ front: 'cold', back: 'つめたい' },
				{ front: 'strong', back: 'つよい' },
				{ front: 'hand', back: 'て' },
				{ front: 'tape', back: 'テープ' },
				{ front: 'tape recorder', back: 'テープレコーダー' },
				{ front: 'table', back: 'テーブル' },
				{ front: 'to go out', back: 'でかける' },
				{ front: 'letter', back: 'てがみ' },
				{ front: 'can', back: 'できる' },
				{ front: 'exit', back: 'でぐち' },
				{ front: 'test', back: 'テスト' },
				{ front: 'then, well', back: 'では' },
				{ front: 'department store', back: 'デパート' },
				{ front: 'but', back: 'でも' },
				{ front: 'to leave', back: 'でます' },
				{ front: 'TV', back: 'テレビ' },
				{ front: 'weather', back: 'てんき' },
				{ front: 'electricity', back: 'でんき' },
				{ front: 'train', back: 'でんしゃ' },
				{ front: 'phone', back: 'でんわ' },
				{ front: 'door', back: 'と' },
				{ front: '~times, ~degree', back: '〜ど' },
				{ front: 'door', back: 'ドア' },
				{ front: 'toilet, lavatory', back: 'トイレ' },
				{ front: 'how?', back: 'どう' },
				{ front: 'why?', back: 'どうして' },
				{ front: 'please, here you are', back: 'どうぞ' },
				{ front: 'animal', back: 'どうぶつ' },
				{ front: 'thanks', back: 'どうも' },
				{ front: 'ten', back: 'とお' },
				{ front: 'far', back: 'とおい' },
				{ front: 'the 10th day of a month, 10 days', back: 'とおか' },
				{ front: 'sometimes', back: 'ときどき' },
				{ front: 'watch, clock', back: 'とけい' },
				{ front: 'where?', back: 'どこ' },
				{ front: 'place', back: 'ところ' },
				{ front: 'library', back: 'としょかん' },
				{ front: 'which, where (polite)', back: 'どちら' },
				{ front: 'very much, quiet', back: 'とても' },
				{ front: 'who (polite)', back: 'どなた' },
				{ front: 'next to', back: 'となり' },
				{ front: 'which?', back: 'どの' },
				{ front: 'to fly', back: 'とぶ' },
				{ front: 'to stop', back: 'とまる' },
				{ front: 'friend', back: 'ともだち' },
				{ front: 'Saturday', back: 'どようび' },
				{ front: 'bird', back: 'とり' },
				{ front: 'chicken meat', back: 'とりにく' },
				{ front: 'to take', back: 'とる' },
				{ front: 'to take a photo', back: 'とる' },
				{ front: 'which?', back: 'どれ' },
				{ front: 'what kind of?', back: 'どんな' },
				{ front: 'knife', back: 'ナイフ' },
				{ front: 'inside', back: 'なか' },
				{ front: 'long', back: 'ながい' },
				{ front: 'to sing, mew, moo', back: 'なく' },
				{ front: 'summer', back: 'なつ' },
				{ front: 'summer vacation', back: 'なつやすみ' },
				{ front: 'and so on', back: '〜など' },
				{ front: 'seven', back: 'ななつ' },
				{ front: 'what?', back: 'なに' },
				{ front: 'the 7th of a month, 7 days', back: 'なのか' },
				{ front: 'name', back: 'なまえ' },
				{ front: 'to learn', back: 'ならう' },
				{ front: 'to form a line', back: 'ならぶ' },
				{ front: 'to line up', back: 'ならべる' },
				{ front: 'to become', back: 'なる' },
				{ front: 'two', back: 'に' },
				{ front: 'lively', back: 'にぎやか' },
				{ front: 'meat', back: 'おにく' },
				{ front: 'west', back: 'にし' },
				{ front: '…st, ..nd, ..th', back: '〜にち' },
				{ front: 'Sunday', back: 'にちようび' },
				{ front: 'luggage', back: 'にもつ' },
				{ front: 'news', back: 'ニュース' },
				{ front: 'garden', back: 'にわ' },
				{ front: '… people', back: '~にん' },
				{ front: 'to take off clothes', back: 'ぬぐ' },
				{ front: 'necktie', back: 'ネクタイ' },
				{ front: 'to go to bed', back: 'ねる' },
				{ front: '~years', back: '〜ねん' },
				{ front: 'notebook', back: 'ノート' },
				{ front: 'to climb up', back: 'のぼる' },
				{ front: 'drinks', back: 'のみもの' },
				{ front: 'to drink', back: 'のむ' },
				{ front: 'to take, to ride', back: 'のる' },
				{ front: 'teeth', back: 'は' },
				{ front: 'party', back: 'パーテイー' },
				{ front: 'yes', back: 'はい' },
				{ front: 'cups of ~', back: '〜はい' },
				{ front: 'ashtray', back: 'はいざら' },
				{ front: 'to enter', back: 'はいる' },
				{ front: 'postcard', back: 'はがき' },
				{ front: 'to put on shoes', back: 'はく' },
				{ front: 'box', back: 'はこ' },
				{ front: 'bridge', back: 'はし' },
				{ front: 'chopsticks', back: 'はし' },
				{ front: 'to begin, to start', back: 'はじまる' },
				{ front: 'start, the beginning', back: 'はじめ' },
				{ front: 'for the first time', back: 'はじめて' },
				{ front: 'to run', back: 'はしる' },
				{ front: 'bus', back: 'バス' },
				{ front: 'butter', back: 'バター' },
				{ front: '20 years old', back: 'はたち' },
				{ front: 'to work', back: 'はたらく' },
				{ front: 'eight', back: 'はち' },
				{ front: 'the 20th of the month, 20 days', back: 'はつか' },
				{ front: 'flower', back: 'はな' },
				{ front: 'nose', back: 'はな' },
				{ front: 'conversation, tale', back: 'はなし' },
				{ front: 'to talk, to speak, to tell', back: 'はなす' },
				{ front: 'my mother', back: 'はは' },
				{ front: 'early', back: 'はやい' },
				{ front: 'fast, quick', back: 'はやい' },
				{ front: 'spring', back: 'はる' },
				{ front: 'to put something on, to stick', back: 'はる' },
				{ front: 'to clear up', back: 'はれる' },
				{ front: 'Half~', back: '〜はん' },
				{ front: 'evening', back: 'ばん' },
				{ front: 'No.~, ranking', back: '〜ばん' },
				{ front: 'bread', back: 'パン' },
				{ front: 'handkerchief', back: 'ハンカチ' },
				{ front: 'number', back: 'ばんごう' },
				{ front: 'dinner', back: 'ばんごはん' },
				{ front: 'half', back: 'はんぶん' },
				{ front: 'east', back: 'ひがし' },
				{ front: 'counter for animals', back: '〜ひき' },
				{ front: 'to pull', back: 'ひく' },
				{ front: 'to play (an instrument)', back: 'ひく' },
				{ front: ' low', back: 'ひくい' },
				{ front: 'plane', back: 'ひこうき' },
				{ front: 'left', back: 'ひだり' },
				{ front: 'person', back: 'ひと' },
				{ front: 'one', back: 'ひとつ' },
				{ front: 'one month', back: 'ひとつき' },
				{ front: 'one person', back: 'ひとり' },
				{ front: 'free time, leisure', back: 'ひま' },
				{ front: 'hundred', back: 'ひゃく' },
				{ front: 'hospital', back: 'びょういん' },
				{ front: 'ill, sick', back: 'びょうき' },
				{ front: 'hiragana characters', back: 'ひらがな' },
				{ front: 'noon', back: 'ひる' },
				{ front: 'lunch', back: 'ひるごはん' },
				{ front: 'wide, spacious', back: 'ひろい' },
				{ front: 'film', back: 'フィルム' },
				{ front: 'envelope', back: 'ふうとう' },
				{ front: 'pool', back: 'プール' },
				{ front: 'fork', back: 'フォーク' },
				{ front: 'to blow (wind)', back: 'ふく' },
				{ front: 'clothes', back: 'ふく' },
				{ front: 'two', back: 'ふたつ' },
				{ front: 'pork', back: 'ぶたにく' },
				{ front: 'two people', back: 'ふたり' },
				{ front: '2nd day of the month, 2 days', back: 'ふつか' },
				{ front: 'thick, fat', back: 'ふとい' },
				{ front: 'to fall (rain, snow)', back: 'ふる' },
				{ front: 'old', back: 'ふるい' },
				{ front: 'bath', back: 'おふろ' },
				{ front: '~minutes', back: '〜ふん' },
				{ front: 'page', back: 'ページ' },
				{ front: 'not good at something', back: 'へた' },
				{ front: 'bed', back: 'ベッド' },
				{ front: 'room', back: 'へや' },
				{ front: 'side, part, area', back: 'へん' },
				{ front: 'pen', back: 'ぺん' },
				{ front: 'to study', back: 'べんきょう' },
				{ front: 'convenient', back: 'べんり' },
				{ front: '~より〜のほうが〜', back: 'ほう' },
				{ front: 'hat', back: 'ぼうし' },
				{ front: 'ballpen', back: 'ボールペン' },
				{ front: 'another, other', back: 'ほか' },
				{ front: 'pocket', back: 'ポケット' },
				{ front: 'to want something', back: 'ほしい' },
				{ front: 'thin, fine', back: 'ほそい' },
				{ front: 'button', back: 'ボタン' },
				{ front: 'hotel', back: 'ホテル' },
				{ front: 'book', back: 'ほん' },
				{ front: 'counter for long objects', back: '~ほん' },
				{ front: 'bookshelf', back: 'ほんだな' },
				{ front: 'really', back: 'ほんとうに' },
				{ front: 'counter for thin objects', back: '〜まい' },
				{ front: 'every morning', back: 'まいあさ' },
				{ front: 'every month', back: 'まいつき/まいげつ' },
				{ front: 'every week', back: 'まいしゅう' },
				{ front: 'every day', back: 'まいにち' },
				{ front: 'every year', back: 'まいとし/まいねん' },
				{ front: 'every evening', back: 'まいばん' },
				{ front: 'front', back: 'まえ' },
				{ front: 'before, in front of', back: '〜まえ' },
				{ front: 'to turn', back: 'まがる' },
				{ front: 'bad tasting', back: 'まずい' },
				{ front: 'also, again', back: 'また' },
				{ front: 'not yet', back: 'まだ' },
				{ front: 'city, town', back: 'まち' },
				{ front: 'to wait', back: 'まつ' },
				{ front: 'straight ahead', back: 'まっすぐに' },
				{ front: 'matches', back: 'マッチ' },
				{ front: 'window', back: 'まど' },
				{ front: 'round', back: 'まるい' },
				{ front: 'ten thousand', back: 'まん' },
				{ front: 'fountain pen', back: 'まんねんひつ' },
				{ front: 'to polish, to brush', back: 'みがく' },
				{ front: 'right', back: 'みぎ' },
				{ front: 'short', back: 'みじかい' },
				{ front: 'water', back: 'おみず' },
				{ front: 'shop', back: 'みせ' },
				{ front: 'to look, to watch', back: 'みせる' },
				{ front: 'road', back: 'みち' },
				{ front: '3rd day of a month, 3 days', back: 'みっか' },
				{ front: 'three', back: 'みっつ' },
				{ front: 'everyone', back: 'みなさん' },
				{ front: 'south', back: 'みなみ' },
				{ front: 'ear', back: 'みみ' },
				{ front: 'to see, to watch', back: 'みる' },
				{ front: 'all, everyone', back: 'みんな' },
				{ front: 'the 6th day of a month, 6 days', back: 'むいか' },
				{ front: 'over there', back: 'むこう' },
				{ front: 'difficult', back: 'むずかしい' },
				{ front: 'six', back: 'むっつ' },
				{ front: 'eye', back: 'め' },
				{ front: 'meter', back: 'メートル' },
				{ front: 'a pair of glasses', back: 'めがね' },
				{ front: 'already, yet', back: 'もう' },
				{ front: '(one) more', back: 'もう' },
				{ front: 'Thursday', back: 'もくようび' },
				{ front: 'hello on the phone', back: 'もしもし' },
				{ front: 'of course', back: 'もちろん' },
				{ front: 'to have, to own', back: 'もつ' },
				{ front: 'more', back: 'もっと' },
				{ front: 'thing', back: 'もの' },
				{ front: 'gate', back: 'もん' },
				{ front: 'problem, question', back: 'もんだい' },
				{ front: 'shop. store', back: '〜や' },
				{ front: 'vegetable shop', back: 'やおや' },
				{ front: 'vegetable', back: 'やさい' },
				{ front: 'gentle', back: 'やさしい' },
				{ front: 'cheap, inexpensive', back: 'やすい' },
				{ front: 'holiday, vacation', back: 'やすみ' },
				{ front: 'to rest', back: 'やすむ' },
				{ front: 'eight', back: 'やっつ' },
				{ front: 'mountain', back: 'やま' },
				{ front: 'to do', back: 'やる' },
				{ front: '8th day of the month, 8 days', back: 'ようか' },
				{ front: 'western style clothing', back: 'ようふく' },
				{ front: 'often', back: 'よく' },
				{ front: 'horizontal', back: 'よこ' },
				{ front: '4th day of the month, 4 days', back: 'よっか' },
				{ front: 'four', back: 'よっつ' },
				{ front: 'to call', back: 'よぶ' },
				{ front: 'to read', back: 'よむ' },
				{ front: 'night', back: 'よる' },
				{ front: 'next month', back: 'らいげつ' },
				{ front: 'next week', back: 'らいしゅう' },
				{ front: 'next year', back: 'らいねん' },
				{ front: 'radio', back: 'ラジオ' },
				{ front: 'splendid', back: 'りっぱ' },
				{ front: 'foreign student', back: 'りゅうがくせい' },
				{ front: 'parents', back: 'りょうしん' },
				{ front: 'cooking', back: 'りょうり' },
				{ front: 'travel', back: 'りょこう' },
				{ front: 'zero', back: 'れい' },
				{ front: 'refrigerator', back: 'れいぞうこ' },
				{ front: 'record', back: 'レコード' },
				{ front: 'restaurant', back: 'レストラン' },
				{ front: 'practice', back: 'れんしゅう' },
				{ front: 'six', back: 'ろく' },
				{ front: 'white shirt', back: 'ワイシャツ' },
				{ front: 'young', back: 'わかい' },
				{ front: 'to know, to understand', back: 'わかる' },
				{ front: 'to forget', back: 'わすれる' },
				{ front: 'me, I', back: 'わたし' },
				{ front: 'to hand over', back: 'わたす' },
				{ front: 'to cross', back: 'わたる' },
				{ front: 'bad', back: 'わるい' }]
	};
});